module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'I ran a 4.6 40 (yard) in high school.', 
    a: 'JLowe',
    b: 'Jenn',
    c: 'West',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'I once got 10 speeding tickets in a single year.', 
    a: 'James',
    b: 'BDF',
    c: 'Brady',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I am a junior park ranger at more than 5 national parks.', 
    a: 'Autumn',
    b: 'Elizabeth',
    c: 'Brendan',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I was nearly suspended from grammar school for making comics about my teachers.', 
    a: 'Billy',
    b: 'Kevin',
    c: 'Brandon T',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I can play all the major scales on the marimba.', 
    a: 'JoCo',
    b: 'Autumn',
    c: 'Jenni',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'When I was younger, I got in trouble for biting a boy that I liked.', 
    a: 'Molly',
    b: 'Mercan',
    c: 'Kendra',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I\'ve been trolling CH people through the Personalization Newsletter shoutouts section.', 
    a: 'Abby',
    b: 'TayTae',
    c: 'Tom',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'My house was on "Walker Texas Ranger."', 
    a: 'Jeremy',
    b: 'Haley',
    c: 'Marion',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'I got straight up stood the f*ck up at prom.', 
    a: 'Mark',
    b: 'Molly',
    c: 'TayTae',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I\'ve performed at Carnegie Hall.', 
    a: 'Abby',
    b: 'Mitch',
    c: 'John',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
